Narrator: 19
Male Speaker: cook dinner
Narrator: 14
Male Speaker: do housework
Narrator: 20
Female Speaker: do exercise
Narrator: 24
Female Speaker: do homework
Narrator: 17
Male Speaker: drink mineral water
Narrator: 23
Female Speaker: drive a car
Narrator: 18
Male Speaker: eat vegetables
Narrator: 9
Female Speaker: go to the cinema
Narrator: 3
Male Speaker: have a garden
Narrator: 8
Female Speaker: like animals
Narrator: 11
Male Speaker: listen to music
Narrator: 6
Female Speaker: live in a flat
Narrator: 22
Male Speaker: need a new passport
Narrator: 12
Male Speaker: play tennis
Narrator: 15
Female Speaker: play the guitar
Narrator: 7
Female Speaker: read a book
Narrator: 16
Male Speaker: say sorry
Narrator: 5
Female Speaker: speak German
Narrator: 4
Male Speaker: study history
Narrator: 13
Female Speaker: take an umbrella
Narrator: 1
Male Speaker: want a coffee
Narrator: 10
Female Speaker: watch TV
Narrator: 21
Male Speaker: wear glasses
Narrator: 2
Female Speaker: work in an office